{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127323178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127323178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127328892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127328892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127339323","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127339323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 9e6b7bd0-f0dc-4ea4-a998-6e8e63cd17db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGA"," userResponse":" NGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127341644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127341644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 9e6b7bd0-f0dc-4ea4-a998-6e8e63cd17db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGA"," userResponse":" NGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127343194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127343194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 9e6b7bd0-f0dc-4ea4-a998-6e8e63cd17db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127351338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127351338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 9e6b7bd0-f0dc-4ea4-a998-6e8e63cd17db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127352935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127352935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 9e6b7bd0-f0dc-4ea4-a998-6e8e63cd17db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127354905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127354904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 9e6b7bd0-f0dc-4ea4-a998-6e8e63cd17db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ngo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127355042","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127355041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 9e6b7bd0-f0dc-4ea4-a998-6e8e63cd17db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127367385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127367385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 445e717d-20b6-40cc-8029-b3551728caf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGA"," userResponse":" NGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127371212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127371212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 445e717d-20b6-40cc-8029-b3551728caf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127372795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127372795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 445e717d-20b6-40cc-8029-b3551728caf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGI"," userResponse":" NGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127373891","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127373891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 445e717d-20b6-40cc-8029-b3551728caf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ngi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127374137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127374137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 445e717d-20b6-40cc-8029-b3551728caf2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGI"," userResponse":" NGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127386421","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127386421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGA"," userResponse":" NGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127390157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127390156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127391719","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127391718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127394897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127394897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127396510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127396510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGI"," userResponse":" NGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127398798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127398798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGI"," userResponse":" NGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127400360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127400360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127403888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127403888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127405502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127405502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGU"," userResponse":" NGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127408474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127408474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127410483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127410483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ngu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127410653","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127410652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127416457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127416457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ngu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127422447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127422447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ngu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127427575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127427575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 7fa34d03-ba8f-4f41-9baa-7dbc20e9b3d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nga..ngu.asc.lc.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ngu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127437848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127437848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127445121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127445120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127449701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127449701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" mwo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127454985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127454984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127459266","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127459266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127463404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127463404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127468988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127468987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127473844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127473844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127479782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127479782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127484502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127484502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127488997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127488997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127494788","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127494785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127501290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127501290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 2f9f3916-87f4-4c51-9d2a-675eec0d8a98"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127522017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127522017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wo_mko_mta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127528647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127528647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ngo_mko_gu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127535278","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127535277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vyi_sho_mko"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127541942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127541942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mko_vya_nu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127548619","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127548619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mwi_fu_mko"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127555261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127555261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_bwa_mbe_mko"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127561911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127561910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mko_two_twa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127568567","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127568566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_no_nye_mko"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127575209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127575209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ndu_ng'u_mko"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127581868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127581868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zo_pe_mko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127595054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127595053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" bf0398e9-9908-4345-acb5-163a0dda21bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.mko..mko.noShow..21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_zo_pe_mko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127604440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127604440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 312e1960-07b4-40d1-a5fd-c8fe11cbda45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127604678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127604677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 312e1960-07b4-40d1-a5fd-c8fe11cbda45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127605642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127605642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 312e1960-07b4-40d1-a5fd-c8fe11cbda45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127605728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127605728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 312e1960-07b4-40d1-a5fd-c8fe11cbda45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549127605811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549127605811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_200829"," gameId":" 312e1960-07b4-40d1-a5fd-c8fe11cbda45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}